hdclix.com 2018-12-21

# Earn Long time and High Profit

Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy is applicable to any personal information, which is submitted via the web site located at HDClix.com.  
We hope the following statement will help you understand how HDClix.com collects, uses and safeguards the personal information you provide to us on our site.

**DATA COLLECTION.**

While using our service at HDClix.com, you may encounter areas in which you are asked to submit User Information.  
This User Information will only be used for the purposes for which it was collected and in accordance with this Privacy Policy.   
During both registration and logging in, your IP address is stored.  
We will never sell, lease or otherwise transfer any personal information obtained from customers to third parties unless required to do so by the law.

**HOW YOUR DATA IS STORED AND USED**

Your email addresses will not be shown, given or sold.  
Your personal email address will only be used for HDClix to communicate with you and to send you a new password in case you request it.  
Your payment processor email addresses will only be used for us to send you your requested payments and to confirm what you purchase.  
Your user password will be stored in an irreversible format.  
Your user password will never be shown, sold or given.

**COOKIES**

Cookies may automatically be used to collect information/data. "Cookies" are small text files that store basic information; for example, display your name/personal details if this has been previously submitted.

**UPDATES**

You may update, amend or correct your personal information which can be found in your "Personal" area in your account Settings (You must be logged in) or you may notify us via the form on the Support page.

**POLICY CHANGE**

We may change this privacy policy from time to time and so therefore, you should check this page regularly.
